<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nitin Ayyagari</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nitin Ayyagari</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building minimal docker images using multi-stage builds</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first_post/</guid>
      <description>With the advancements in world of containers, it is now easier and &amp;amp; feasible for you to deploy containerized applications.&#xA;Docker is a utility to efficiently create, ship, and run containers. They enable isolation and portability of application. However, one of the challenges of building docker images is to hold down the image size. One of the most effective ways to optimise the image sizes is to use multi stage builds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep Calm and Index Everything</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/second_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/second_post/</guid>
      <description>This post was originally written on lambda.grofers.com&#xA;Currently at Grofers we are growing rapidly. And with this rapid-growth comes a huge amount of data. As we all know the (not so) famous saying:&#xA;With great amount of data comes an itching need to analyse it.&#xA;As the size of our data is growing rapidly, we have to analyse the trends that push our product forward.&#xA;We use PostgreSQL as our primary datastore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/general/sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/general/sample/</guid>
      <description>History Sample Blüdhaven was a former whaling town, which was officially incorporated as a &amp;ldquo;Commonwealth&amp;rdquo; in 1912. The town had a generally poor socio-economic populace, owing in part to failed efforts to transform itself into a manufacturing and shipping center.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
